声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：skier_airman校对：扣扣
后期：阿胜 双语制作：sealovemoon  憨妹 闲逛
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
先生?
Sir?
请开一下门
I'm gonna have to ask that you open the door, please.
我们能不能谈些其它的事?
How about we talk about that other thing?
如你们所知  阿拉伯人靠他的破接收机检测到了信号
You know, the transmission Abdul picked up on his little radio.
信号中的法国妞说  "他们都已经死了"
The french chick that said "they're all dead."
我们回到岸边后就得把这一切告诉他们
We have to tell the others when we get back.
什么事都不能跟他们说
No one's going to tell them anything.
如果我们把知道的都告诉了他们
If we tell them what we know
我们会夺走他们仅存的希望
we take away their hope.
所以  我们得说谎了
So we lie.
现在我已经找到了淡水 就在山谷里
Now I found fresh water up in the valley.
我会先带一队人上去取水
I'll take a group in at first light.
如果你不想来  做点其它事也可以 只要能为团队做贡献就行
If you don't want to go, then find another way to contribute,
因为要是只顾自己的话在这里已经行不通了
because every man for himself is not gonna work.
打扰一下
excuse me.
你看到我的孩子了吗?
have you seen my boy?
我... 要... 去打猎
I... am going off... away to a hunt.
我在想你是否...
And I was wondering if you...
能够...帮忙照看一下我的孩子
could, keep an eye on my boy
直到我打猎回来
until I come back.
你不介意  是吧?
You're cool with this, right?
我不是想问你私人问题
It's not like I'm asking you a personal question.
我只是想知道...
Ijust want to know.
-你没必要知道  -说出来听听又有什么关系?
-Well, you're not gonna know.  -What's the big deal?
是没什么关系 只不过我干了些事罢了
It's not a big deal. It's just something I did.
有些事我搞不明白不得不在那儿解决
I have my reasons, and I don't want to put it out there.
只是你的为人
It's just that you
和你的纹身似乎并不匹配
and your tattoos don't add up.
你属于那种中坚的脊骨外科医生?
Are you one of those hardcore spinal surgeons?
说的对  "中坚力量"
That's me. Hardcore.
你俩说完了吧 我们得出发了
If you guys are finished verbally copulating, we should get a move on.
整个海滩的人都在等着我们取水
There's a whole beach of people waiting for us to get some drinking water for them.
那打猎高手根本不用休息
And the great white hunter's getting restless.
好吧  我们出发
Okay, let's do this.
Charlie
问问Jack关于纹身的事
ask Jack about his tattoos.
你们还有内部笑话啊
you guys have an inside joke.
你俩可真行啊
How absolutely wonderful for you both.
想要杯香槟吗?
你有东西落下了
真的吗?
是什么呢?
我的父亲?
他现在忙着做东呢
我们得离开这里  现在就走
去哪儿呢?
美国
Sun  看着我  我爱你...
但我不想和你私奔
这是我们唯一的机会了
你父亲永远都不会同意的
他又没权利来同意这是我们的决定
我会去跟你父亲谈的
我会让他明白的
你这样说就是因为你不了解我父亲的为人
但你了解我呀
真漂亮
我希望它能变成一块钻石
相信有一天会的
出什么事了?
怎么...
what the...
住手! 住手!
Stop! stop!
求你放开他!
Get off of him! Please!
住手!
Stop!
住手!放开他!
Stop! Get off of him!
你做点什么呀! 他会杀了我爸的!
Do something! He's gonna kill him!
求你让他停手!
Stop him, please!
让他停手呀!
他会杀了他的!
He's gonna kill him!
用军官的手铐铐住他!
The handcuffs from the sky marshal!Now!
怎么回事?
What happened?
水在这边
Water's this way.
怎么给你找到这地方的?
How'd you find this place?
运气
Luck.
就这儿
This is it.
不可思议
It's amazing.
是的  和你一样另人惊奇
Absolutely. It's totally you.
伙计们?
guys?
要不要在这找找?
Shouldn't someone look through this stuff?
或许能找到些有用的东西
Could be something useful in here.
他真有头脑
He's got a point.
-是吗?  -是的
-I do?  -Yeah.
把你的瓶子给我
Bring me your bottles
留意一下医疗用品  尤其是药
Keep an eye out for any medical supplies, drugs in particular.
药?  好的
Drugs. Right.
不要动
Don't move.
-听着,我只是想....  -不要动
-Look, I was just gonna take  -Do not move.
-发生什么事了?  -嘘...
-What's going on?  -Shh.
他站在一个蜂窝上面
He's standing on a beehive.
蜂窝怎么会在这儿?
What's a beehive doing there?
不是应该在树上的吗!
Beehives are supposed to be in trees.
现在该怎么办?
What now?
如果他动一下  会把蜂窝弄破的
If he moves, he'll split the hive.
我一点儿都不喜欢蜜蜂  明白?
I don't like bees, okay?
我对蜜蜂有种无名的恐惧
I have an irrational fear of bees
-我想我会过敏  -安静点儿
-I think I'm allergic to bees.  -Please be quiet.
得找东西把蜂窝封起来
We need to get something to seal the hive.
-盖住它?  -是的  快!
-To cover it?  -Yeah. Hurry!
我已经说得烦了
I'm getting tired of saying this.
刚才  我和儿子正在海边走
I was just walking the beach with my son
突然  那野人向我扑来
and all of a sudden this dude is all up on me.
我什么事都没做过
I didn't do anything.
有些事  你当然不会告诉我们
Surely there must be something you're not telling us.
当真?!
Surely?!
你哪里人  伙计?!
Where you from, man?!
提克里特
Tikrit.
伊拉克
Iraq.
好吧  我不知道在伊拉克碰到这种情况会怎样
Okay, I don't know how it is in Iraq
但在美国  我的家乡
but in the United States of America where I'm from
韩国人是不喜欢黑人的
korean people don't like black people.
你知不知道?
You know that?
要谈话  你应该找他!
So maybe you ought to talk to him!
先铐着再说
The cuffs stay on.
阿拉伯  说大声一点 或许那样她听得懂
A little louder, Omar. Maybe then she'll understand you.
伙计们  这样做的话 那中国佬会疯的
Guys, that chinese dude's gonna get pretty crispy out here.
你们要铐他到什么时候?
How long you gonna keep him tied down like that?
他差点杀了Michael  大家都看到了
He tried to kill Michael. We all saw it.
等我们搞清楚事情原委再帮他解开
The cuffs stay on until we know why.
儿子  我们走
Come on, man. Let's go.
发生什么了?
是这样的...
你的父亲...
你的父亲同意了
别再这样了!
你怎么办到的?
我跟他讲道理啊
经过一年的管理业务训练
外加在工厂做工一年
我们需要的钱都赚到了
你要帮我爸干活?
这样做是对的
我不得不这样做
这只是临时的
你可买不起这个的
现在可以了哦
好
Okay.
不要动
Just keep still, man.
我想办法把蜂窝盖起来
I'm gonna try to cover the hive.
这真是个馊主意  不管用的
This is the most crap idea ever.It's never gonna work.
合作一点  孩子
Pull yourself together, son.
即使我合作了
It wouldn't be an irrational fear of bees
还是消除不了我对蜜蜂的恐惧难道不是吗?
if I could just pull myself together, would it?
他是谁?  怎么会在这儿?
Who is he? How'd he get here?
虽然不能解剖尸体  但是
Can't exactly perform an autopsy,but
看起来并不像是由严重骨伤引起的
doesn't seem to be any major trauma to the bones.
这儿还有一具
There's another one over here.
有人把他们搁在这儿休息
Someone laid them to rest here.
-谁?  -我不知道
-Who?  -I don't know.
他们是从哪儿来的?
Where'd they come from?
上周你们不是打死一只北极熊吗?
Didn't you guys shoot a polar bear last week?
是的
Yeah.
熊是从哪里来的?
Where'd that come from?
能否知道这两具尸体放在这儿已经多久了?
Any idea how long they've been here?
很长时间了  衣服都腐蚀成这至少有40或50年了
Long. It takes 40 or 50 years for clothing to degrade like this.
那是什么?
What is it?
有人吗?
Hello! Anybody there?
大家都没事吧?
Everyone all right?
就边上被叮了几口
A few stings aside.
你俩跑得可真快啊!
You two run away fantastically.
我跑得慢  蜜蜂都来我这儿了你们才幸以逃脱
Glad my diversion spared you.
只有我  不知道被叮了多少口
I was only stung several hundred times.
而且...
and
有人把这个落下了
someone left this.
这...里面都是蜜蜂
It was,it was full of bees.
我想应该是"C"罩
I'd have thought c's, actually.
抱歉
Sorry.
天哪
Bloody hell.
原来我们之前  就已经有人来过了
These are the people who were here before us.
你说什么?
What are you talking about?
只是...
just
有...
you know, there...
这些人应该是在我们之前来的  对吧?
there could have been people here before us, right?
当然
Clearly.
这些家伙是什么人?
But who were these men?
事实上  其中一位是女性
Actually, one of them's female.
这座孤岛上的亚当和夏娃
Our very own Adam and Eve.
你在做什么呀
你的皮肤都破了
当心点
觉得怎么样?
喜欢吗?
我工作的时间很长我觉得你会喜欢这个伙伴的
当然你得训练它  喂养它
你没事吧?
记得以前的日子吗?你给我的只是一朵小花
是你父亲的电话
我想我们得留一个帮Charlie整理飞机残骸
I think one of us should stay and help Charlie salvage the wreckage.
你想留下?
You offering?
是的
Sure.
给自己个机会多了解他一点
Give me a chance to get to know him a little better.
我们得走了
We should move out.
很可能人们已经等得口渴了
People are probably getting thirsty.
怎么了?
What?
46个人每人每天得喝掉半加仑水
46 people need to drink a half gallon a day each.
扛着这些水跑来跑去实在太痛苦了
Carrying all this water back and forth is gonna be a real pain in the ass.
你这么一说我确实是有点后悔了
You're starting to make me regret volunteering.
这些洞穴是个安身的好地方而不像是一个坟地
These caves make too good a shelter just to be used for burial.
亚当和夏娃他们一定在这儿住过
Adam and Eve, they must have lived here.
可能是飞机坠毁也可能是船只失事
Their plane crashed, or maybe they were shipwrecked.
他们找到了这个地方以为在这儿或许可以活下来
They probably found this place and knew they could survive here.
源源不断的淡水
Unlimited supply of fresh water.
树阴使得温度不会太高
Tree canopy keeps the temperature down
还遮住了太阳
shields out the sun.
出口很窄
The openings are narrow.
很容易躲避食肉动物的攻击
Easier for protection against predators.
我们没必要把水带到海边
We don't need to bring the water to the people.
我们只需把人们带过来
We need to bring the people to the water.
我想我们可以在这儿居住
I think we could live here.
你在干什么?
what are you doing?
你是不是对我儿子说了什么?
You say something to my boy?
是的  也很高兴和你谈话
Yeah, nice talking to you, too
我们走  Walt
Let's move it, Walt.
他为什么不喜欢我们?
How come he doesn't like us?
你刚才说他那种人不喜欢我们
You said people like him don't like people like us.
不
No.
事情不是这样的  知道吗?
Look, that's...that's not true, and you know what?
我也不想这么说的 我只是...
I don't think like that anyway. I was...
我只是生气罢了
I was angry.
你对他做过什么?
What'd you do to him?
我对他做过什么?
What did I do to him?
你说呢!
You tell me.
自从飞机失事后 我就一直和你在一起
I've been with you since we crashed.
你看到我对什么人做过什么不该做的事吗?
Have you seen me do anything to anyone?
你到底是怎么看我的?
What kind of man do you think I am anyway?
你妈妈是不是对你说了什么?
What did your mother say about me?
她从来不和我说你的事儿
She never talked about you.
就是说你一点儿都不了解我  是吧?
You don't know anything about me then, do you?
你也一样不了解我
You don't know anything about me.
我很了解你
I know a lot about you.
-是吗?  -是的
-Yeah?  -Yeah.
-我生日什么时候?  -8月24号
-When's my birthday?  -August 24th.
我的呢?
When's mine?
算了  走吧
Forget it. Come on, man.
亲爱的  求求你了就让我去跟他们解释一下吧
或许他们会放过你的
你要怎么解释?
你就呆在我旁边
而且我们也不会跟那个贼解释什么的
你没事吧
跟我好好谈谈吧
你受伤了?
你怎么了?
你在做什么呀?
这是谁的血?
发生什么事了?
我在工作
在做什么事?
你为我爸做的都是些什么事?
看着我
回答我
你爸说什么  我就做什么
我做的这一切都是为了我们两个
你胡思乱想?
You checking me out?
什么?
What?
-这么想也没什么坏处  只是  -相信我
-There's no harm in it. I just  -Trust me,
如果我那么想  我会让你知道的
if I was checking you out, you'd know it.
是吗?  那么你在想什么?就现在的想法
Yeah? So then what were you thinking? Right now.
我发誓我没朝那方面想
Well, I sure as hell wasn't thinking that.
继续想...就跟我说吧
Don't stop to think. Just... tell me.
我在想
I was thinking
如果我们住在洞边可以在泉水上方筑个水坝
that if we were living at the caves, we could build a damn around that spring
那样每个人都可以喝到淡水了
so that everybody could have fresh water
而且医务室也可以搬过来
and we could get the infirmary off the beach.
你认为这主意不好?
You think it's a bad idea?
很好  很不错的主意
No, it makes sense.
但?
But?
-没有但是  -很好
-No but.  -Good.
大部分人一直盼望着救援队的到来
Because a lot of people are still hoping a rescue boat's gonna show up.
他们一点都没考虑过自己的安全问题
They're not thinking about their own safety.
我们还有许多说服工作要做
We're gonna have a lot of convincing to do.
我们?
We?
你甚至连我都没说服呢!
You still haven't convinced me yet.
你要跟着我?
You following me?
是的
Yes.
不必了  我只是去上上厕所
There's no need. I'm just going to the loo.
你是不是想告诉我一些事情  Charlie?
Is there something you want to tell me, Charlie?
我要去厕所
I'm going to the loo.
那儿很危险
It's dangerous out there.
在回到岸边之前我不会让你离开我的视线
Until we get back to the beach, I'm not breaking line of sight with you.
离我远点
Bugger off.
我知道你是谁 我也知道你在找什么
I know who you are, and I know what you're looking for.
"驱轴乐队"
Driveshaft.
你是低音手
You played bass.
也是吉他手
And guitar.
在有几首歌里面弹奏过的
On a couple of tracks.
你真的听说过我们?
You really heard of us?
我是过40了 但也不能说明我是个聋子啊
Hey, just because I'm over 40 doesn't mean I'm deaf.
我有两张你们的专集
I have both your albums.
尽管我认为
Although I thought
你的初次登台比"律动的油"(某乐队名)要强多了
that your self-titled debut was a much stronger effort than "oil change."
乐队发生这样的事实在是太遗憾了
It's a shame what happened to the band.
你已经多久没碰吉他了?
How long since you played?
我的吉他
My guitar...
差不多有8天11个小时了
8 days, 11 hours, give or take.
你想它了?
You miss it?
这儿还有很多残留物 或许可以找到一把
Well, a lot of wreckage. It might still turn up.
没损坏?  还可以弹奏?不可能找的到的
Undamaged? Still playable? I don't think so.
我当然希望找到它但登机前核对我的那家伙是个混蛋
I mean, I wish, but there was this bloke at the counter made me check it in.
她说客舱里没足够空间了就像个法西斯一样
wasn't enough roomin the cabin. Fascist.
你会再见到你的吉他的
You will see it again.
是吗?
yeah?
为什么这么说?
What makes you say that?
因为我有信仰  Charlie
Because I have faith, Charlie.
总算来了
It's about time.
我都快渴死了
I am dying of thirst.
我想我得让他在太阳底下多呆会儿
I think I'll let him sit in the sun a while longer.
然后我会把他妻子拉到一边
Then I'll take his wife aside
设法和她沟通
find some way to communicate.
我想她知道为什么他要攻击Michael
I think she knows why he attacked Michael.
真不用着我去和她谈?
You sure you don't want me to talk to her?
好吧
Okay.
你把那件事解决了
If you've got that under control
我就和人们谈关于山洞的事
I'm gonna start talking to people about the caves.
可能的话夜幕降临前就带些人过去
Might be able to get a few to go with me before nightfall
在那扎营
start setting up camp.
你是认真的?
You're serious?
你要开辟自己的文明时代却不和我们商量一下?
Is there a reason you didn't consult us when you decided to form your own civilization?
我只是说搬到山谷那儿去
I'm only talking about moving into the valley.
你上次还说大家要呆在一起  独自死去?
Well, what happened to live together, die alone?
大家一块儿把工作做好是唯一的生存之道
Digging in together is the only way we're gonna survive.
我们要活下去  最幸运的就是被飞机或船只发现我们困在这里
Our best hope of survival is in being spotted by a plane or a ship.
而如果要让别人发现的话  我们得组织大家不停的用火焰发射信号
And for that, we need to organize everyone to keep that signal fire burning
而另外一些人得在岛上找食物
while others scout the island for supplies.
在其它地方扎营  那是一种自杀
Digging in anywhere else is suicide.
那是我们找到的唯一的淡水源地  Sayid
It is the only source of freshwater we've found, Sayid.
呆在海边  太阳底下没有水喝...
And staying on the beach, in the sun, without water...
难道那就不是自杀?
that's not suicide?
我还没有放弃希望
I'm not going to admit defeat.
又怎么了?
Now what?
事情我已经说得很清楚了  老大
I already gave you my statement, sheriff.
我是来道歉的 我不应该这么疑神疑鬼
I came to apologize. I shouldn't have been suspicious.
今天早上  你才是受害者
You were the victim in the attack this morning.
很感谢你这么说
I appreciate that
不过我敢说你专程跑来不会是来跟我道歉的
but I can tell you didn't come all the way over here just to say you're sorry.
人们都在考虑跟随Jack去山洞住
People are seriously considering following Jack to the caves.
我想知道你是怎么想的
I'd like to know where you stand.
我要呆在这儿
Right here.
现在最重要的事是尽快让我的孩子离开这个岛
I got one priority right now, and that's getting my kid off this island.
要是有船只经过我就不想错过这样的机会
A boat passes, I'm not gonna be on the hook for missing it.
慢慢喝  每次少喝一点省着点喝
Slowly. Just a little bit at a time. Little bit.
很高兴你也一块来
Glad you're coming.
伙计  野猪在哪  我就去哪
man, I go where the boar's at.
那么...
So...
你和Kate有什么进展?
what up with you and Kate?
你俩会去山洞里同居  还是怎样?
You guys gonna move into a cave together, or what?
-什么  我还像高中生那样?  -就是说你不否认了?
-Sorry, am I in high school?  -Well, that wasn't a denial.
快点整理  我们马上就出发
Just get your stuff together. We got to get out of here soon.
这不是我们的舞会美女么
If it ain't the belle of the ball.
医生和军官为你而战感觉怎么样?
So what's it like, having both the doctor and captain falafel fighting over you?
我是这么看他们的雀斑女
Just call'em how I see 'em, freckles.
实话说
Truth be told
我和别人一样都很好奇你是怎么看待
I'm not the only one wondering where you're gonnan weigh in on this whole
搬离海滩这样的事
moving off the beach thing.
你要和那个悲观的家伙一块去?
Are you going with the pessimists
还是呆在这儿  等着救援的到来?
or staying here and waiting for the rescue boats?
你会去吗?
Are you going?
这真是个小把戏  不是吗?
Well, that's the real trick, isn't it?
如果我们都把赌注压在去山洞
We all pack up stakes for the caves
第2天  一架飞机高兴地飞过小岛
next day a plane passes by
那样的话  大家都会傻愣眼
they're gonna go on their merry way and be none the wiser.
相反  如果呆在这儿 被野猪吃掉  或被山石砸死
On the other hand, stay here, get eaten by boars, fall off a rock
至少还可能碰到来救援的
not gonna be anyone around to answer that 911 call.
你还没有回答我的问题
You still haven't answered my question.
你也没回答我的
You didn't answer mine.
而且是我先问的
And I asked first.
你丈夫不反对出钱重新装修这儿
你真是个幸运的妻子
是啊
把狗拿开
让我们去看看卧室吧  好吗?
你确定要这样做吗?
确定
你上过课了?
上过了
你知道你父亲和你丈夫会不顾一切地找你吗?
你确定你跟你丈夫和解不了了吗?
我走了以后你能帮我照顾我的狗吗?
在机场里  11点15分
找个借口出机场
什么也别带
有辆车会等你的
接下来的一个礼拜你的家人会认为你被绑架了
你要继续躲着直到他们认为你已经死了
从那以后你就可以自由地去任何地方了
那么  再跟我复述一下时间吧
机场  11点15分
再说一次
11点15分
太好了  看谁来了
great. Look who came to chat.
我得和你谈谈
I need to talk to you.
你会说英语?
You speak english?
什么  你会说英语?
What...you speak english?
为什么你以前不说?
Why didn't you say anything?
我丈夫不知道我会说英语
My husband doesn't know.
你会英语为什么不能告诉你丈夫?
Why would you learn english and not tell your husband?
他脾气很坏
He has a bad temper.
今天我丈夫这么做
What my husband did to you today...
其实是一个误解
it was a misunderstanding.
我可明白他这样做的原因 清清楚楚  明明白白
No, I got it. Loud and clear.
是因为手表的原因
It was the watch.
你丈夫为了一只表居然要谋杀我?
Your husband tried to murder me for a watch?
这表是我在两天前找到的
I found this watch two days ago.
这是我父亲的表
It belongs to my father.
保护那只手表是一个尊严问题
Protecting that watch is a question of honor.
你认为在我孩子面前杀我是很尊严的行为?
You call trying to kill me in front of my kid honor?
你不了解我的父亲
You don't know my father.
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
听我说  你这老怪物
Listen to me, you old geek.
我要去丛林
I'm going in the jungle.
一个男人...
A man has...
有权保护自己的隐私
a right to some privacy.
只要把它给我就行
Just hand it to me.
你会被耗尽的
You're gonna run out.
与其说以后  不如说很快
My guess is sooner rather than later.
痛苦地戒毒过程是在所难免的
Painful detox is inevitable.
但如果现在就开始戒毒至少这是你自己的选择
Give it up now. At least it'll be your choice.
不要这样跟我说话好象你什么都知道似的
Don't talk to me like you know something about me.
我受过的苦  你难以想象
I know a lot more about pain than you think.
我并不嫉妒你现在所面对的
I don't envy what you're facing
但是我想帮助你
but I want to help
你想要你的吉他吗?
Do you want your guitar?
甚于毒品?
More than your drug?
你想象不到我有多么想要
More than you know.
就我所知  如果你在寻找什么这座岛屿就会给你什么
What I know is that this island just might give you what you're looking for
但前提是你也得给这座岛一些东西
but you have to give the island something.
你真的能找到我的吉他?
You really think you can find my guitar?
往上看  Charlie
Look up, Charlie.
你不会要我祈祷吧
You're not gonna ask me to pray or something.
我要你往上看
I want you to look up.
该出发了
It's almost time to go.
我不想成为夏娃
I don't want to be Eve.
没人要你成为夏娃
No one's asking you to.
我只是不能...
I just can't...
有人得留这儿站岗等着救援的到来
Someone else can stay here, keep a look out, wait for rescue.
为什么一定要是你?
Why does it have to be you?
-不是这个原因  -那是什么原因?
-That's not it.  -Then what is it?
Kate  为什么你要这样?
Kate, how did you get to be this way?
你这么做有什么原因吗?
Just what is it that you did?
你会明白的
You had your chance to know.
如果需要我的话你知道在哪可以找到我
If you need me, you know where to find me.
你也知道去哪儿找我
You know where to find me, too.
我知道你听不懂
I know you can't understand a word
一般说来我也不是那种"大嗓门"的人
and normally I'm not the talking-out-loud type
但既然你在听
but since I have a captive audience
为了你自己  你好好给我听着
I hope for your sake you pay attention.
这个月我过得并不好
I'm not exactly having the best month of my life.
我几乎不了解我的儿子而现在我得做他的爸爸
I barely know my son, and now I gotta be his daddy.
撇开那不说
And then to top it off
居然有个神经错乱的韩国佬想杀我  为什么呢?!
I have a deranged korean guy trying to kill me, and for what?!
我现在算是明白了
I get it. Right
是为了只只手表我自己的坏了 我在残骸里找到的
It's the watch. Mine broke. I found this in the wreckage,
我就想怎么能让一块价值2万美圆的手表变成垃圾?
and I figured, hey, why let a $20,000 watch go to waste?
不过实在是太可笑了在这该死的岛上知道时间有什么用啊!
Which is ridiculous, since time doesn't matter on a damn island!
该死的....
Son of a...
离我远点...
Stay away from me...
还有我的儿子
and my kid.
我必须在16小时内赶到L.A.X.
16 hours, I need to land at L.A.X.
而且我必须得让灵柩通过海关
And I need that coffin to clear customs
因为那儿将会有灵车等着而且那灵车...
because there's gonna be a hearse waiting, and I need that hearse...
出事了吗?
花真是太漂亮了
有人吗!
Hello!
怎么回事?
What's this?
新居民
New tenants.
很近?!  骗人!!
Short walk. They lied.
我能问你件事吗?
Could I ask you something?
随便问  儿子
Anything you want, man.
你什么时候生日?
When's your birthday?
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====